docplayer.net 2018-10-05

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated: May 24, 2018

## 1\. Introduction

We strongly respect your privacy. This Privacy Notice details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User information collected on the Docplayer.net website. Docplayer.net (also referred as to Us) provides this Privacy Notice to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using Docplayer.net. Docplayer.net reserves the right to amend the privacy policy at any time. In case of such amendment, Docplayer.net shall publishes a relevant notification of such changes on the official Web-Site. To continue usage of the Docplayer.net’s services, You will be asked to fill consent application.

Docplayer.net shall gather Personal information only in scope, that is required for providing You with relevant services and that confirms with purposes of such collection.

Docplayer.net shall gather Personal information only for purposes, that are stipulated in this Privacy Policy, or requirements, that follow from applicable law.

We don’t process Your Personal Information longer, then it is required by applicable law.

We do not transfer Your Personal Data to third Parties, except cases, that are mentioned in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Docplayer.net Terms of Use. Your use of the Docplayer.net website and any personal information you provide on Docplayer.net remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use.

## 2\. Personal Information

We will not give, sell or rent your email address, or any other personal information to third parties at time for any reason without Your prior consent or request for it. Docplayer.net reserves the right to transfer your personal data to third parties only under official request of competent state bodies, Law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when Docplayer.net is compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order, or similar legal procedure; or under other obligatory provisions, that are stipulated in applicable law.

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, to administer User accounts (Accounts) (together, the Service) and to enable Visitors to enjoy and easily navigate the Docplayer.net.

Considering the fact, that PI includes all information, that can anyway conduce Your identification, we gather next categories of PI about You:

When you register with us through the Docplayer.net, or when you choose to add information to your profile or elect to submit your personal information to third parties through the Docplayer.net and the Services, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you (Personal Information). Personal Information (also referred as to PI) may include: your name, email address, and certain information related to your social networks, including login credentials, information regarding web-site’s personal account registration.

Moreover, we collect and store information about posted by Yourself presentations. Such information is deemed to be public since it has been posted. We also gather information regarding messages, that You send us.

We bear no responsibility for re-publishing of previously deleted materials (presentations) by other Users as during first publishing they (materials) became public.

For providing ability to use Our services without creating an user account, we collect additional information about You, including, but not limited to information regarding Your device, Your IP address, information about Your Web-browser (for statistics purposes and for improving of the Web-site).

## 3\. Personal Data processing purposes

We use your Personal Information only:

  * to provide the Services,
  * to administer yours inquiries and requests,
  * maintaining of statistics,
  * for improvement of our Web-site,
  * for personalization of content, that is proposed to You.

You can decide not to submit personal information, in which case we won't be able to make the Docplayer.net services available to you

## 4\. Your rights

You have the right to receive information regarding purposes of Personal information collection, regarding third parties, to which we disclose Your personal information, information, regarding safeguards that are applicable for secure storage of Your Personal information, period of time for which Persona information will be stored.

You also have the right to demand erasure of personal data concerning You. Docplayer.net shall fulfill Your demand in appropriate period of time. If there is no other lawful ground for storing and processing of Your PI, as prescribed in applicable law, Docplayer.net shall erase such information. If there is another legal ground for such processing, Docplayer.net shall notify You in appropriate period of time.

You also have the right to demand restriction of the storing and processing of the PI, if legal grounds for such demands have arisen / as prescribed in applicable law.

You have the right to object processing of personal data concerning Yourself under circumstances, that are prescribed in applicable law. In case of such objection, Docplayer.net shall restrain from processing of Your PI, if there will be no other legal grounds for continuing of processing.

You have the right to ask Docplayer.net for providing You with a structured, list of previously provided PI. You also can ask Docplayer.net to transmit Your PI to previously chosen third party.

## 5\. Collection of Children’s PI

Children can only use our services under the supervision of their parents/legal guardians and we always suggest minors (under the age of 16) not to submit any personal information to us or use the service. Consent for processing of minor’ PI shall be given by their holder of parental responsibility over the minor.

Personal Docplayer.net does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Docplayer.net website from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Docplayer.net website at any time or in any manner. If Docplayer.net learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on the Docplayer.net website without verified parental consent, then Docplayer.net will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

## 6\. Cookies

When you visit the Docplayer.net website, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Docplayer.net uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Your browser may use persistent cookies on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following the directions in your web browser's help file. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when it receives a cookie. However, some features of the Docplayer.net website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

We show You the Cookie-banner for receiving of Your appropriate consent for usage of Cookies. You are able to restrict our usage of Cookies anytime in Your profile settings. It is impossible to maintain our web-site without minimal usage of Cookies and this is why we show You the Cookie-banner. We use required Cookies even if You do not except banner.

## 7\. Usage of Personal Information

Our privacy policy applies only to the Docplayer.net website. Docplayer.net contains links to other sites and file downloads from other sites. We do not exercise control over any site that may be linked to from within content on this site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such web sites.

We do not transfer Your Personal Data to third Parties, except cases, that are mentioned in this Privacy Policy.We work with other third-party companies, that help us to provide or improve our services, or use advertisements and related with it services. Thanks to this cooperation, we are able to work and to provide free of charge services around the world.

We transfer Your PD to third-party services Google Adsens and Google Analytics for maintain of Website functioning, for content personification and for showing of personilised advertisements.

If you submit personally identifiable information to us through the Docplayer.net website, then we may use your personal information to operate, maintain, and provide features and functionality of the Docplayer.net website.

Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual is collected by Docplayer.net from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of use) and is exclusively owned by Docplayer.net. Docplayer.net can use this information in such manner that Docplayer.net, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

We may share specific aggregated, non-personal information with third parties, such as the number of users who have registered with us, the volume and pattern of traffic to and within the site, etc. That information will not identify you, the individual, in any way.

Any personal information or video and textual content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and comments, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload files or send messages through the Docplayer.net website and other Users can contact you through messages and comments. Any content that you submit to the Docplayer.net website may be viewed by the general public.

When you use the Docplayer.net website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, internet protocol (IP) address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

## 8.Public information

We are empowered to disclose or transfer Your public information, such as information from Your user account, public releases [publications]. Remember, You are able to control the publicity of Your releases, publications, publicity of Your another information with help of privacy settings. Other information, such as Your name, nickname are always public.

When we transfer PI outside the European Union or EFTA, we ensure, that the adequate level of PI security is provided. During such transfer, we also ensure, that adequate level of Your rights protection is also applied, basing on adequacy analysis of the third country personal data protection legislation, basing on contractual obligations, assumed by the PI recipient.

If at any time in the future, we propose to use personal information for any purpose other than our internal use in maintaining the services, troubleshooting, improving our services, etc., then we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes.

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Docplayer.net site changes or for customer service purposes).

We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

You can control and manage PI, that is being provided to the Docplayer.net via Your personal account by changing privacy settings anytime.

You may update or correct your personal profile information and email preferences at any time by visiting your account profile page. You can also close your account on the Docplayer.net website. If you close your Docplayer.net account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by applicable law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Docplayer.net Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the Docplayer.net service, please send your request. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with Docplayer.net under your name.

When you send email or other communication to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. We won't share any information you send to us in those communications with any third parties.

We use cookies and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Docplayer.net; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

## 9.Protection of the Personal Information

Docplayer.net uses store and process Your PI on Docplayer.nets servers in various jurisdictions, where our facilities and/or service providers are located. By filling a “consent application “You agree to this transfer, storing, or processing. Docplayer.net will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your Personal Data is treated securely and in accordance with this Policy. Docplayer.net protect Your Personal Data under internationally acknowledged standards, using physical, technical, and administrative security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, and alteration. Some of the safeguards Docplayer.net use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. Docplayer.net also authorize access to Personal Data only for those employees or contractors who require it to fulfill their job or service responsibilities. All of our physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards are designed to comply with applicable laws and regulations. Third parties may be located in other countries where the laws on processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than in Your country. From time to time, the Personal Data may be also stored in other locations, and in such cases, Docplayer.net will ensure that the Personal Data will be stored and processed with the reasonable level of care and security.

We also point your attention to the fact that we are obliged to make back-ups. Therefore, Your PD is also kept in such back-ups with respect to all safety and legal requirements.

We store PD in logs during 3 weeks. We store Your PD in back-ups during 5 years. Moreover, Your PD are also stored in Google Analitycs during 50 months.

## 10.Notification

In the case of a personal data breach, Docplayer.net shall without undue delay and, where feasible, not later than 72 hours after having become aware of it, notify the personal information breach to the supervisory compent authority, unless the personal information breach is unlikely to result in a risk to the rights and freedoms of natural persons.

If Docplayer.net learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Docplayer.net may post a notice on the Docplayer.net website if a security breach occurs.

When the personal data breach is likely to result in a high risk to the rights and freedoms of users, the Docplayer.net shall send a warning emails (that have been previously provided) to users, PI of which may be exposed.

In the event that Docplayer.net is acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from our Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will notify Users before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

## 11\. Amendments to the Privacy Policy

Please note that this privacy policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. To continue usage of the Docplayer.net’s services, You will be asked to fill consent application.

## 12\. Contact us

If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us or to write to us at: [privacy@docplayer.net](mailto:privacy@docplayer.net)
